The prediction is basically the answer we get from the algorithm.
预测的结果就是通过算法计算后得到的结果
A discreet answer will be of the form yes, no.
离散答案就是 “是” 或者 “否” 的形式
Whereas a continued answer will be a number,
而连续答案将是一个数字
normally between zero and one which we'll consider a probability.
通常在 0 到 1 的范围之间 我们称之为概率
In the running example,
在这个例子中
here we have our students where blue is accepted and red is rejected.
蓝色表示被录取的学生 红色表示被拒的学生
And the discrete algorithm will tell us if a student is accepted or rejected
离散算法将告诉我们学生是录取还是被拒了
by typing a zero for rejected students and a one for accepted students.
用 0 表示被拒 用 1 表示被录取
On the other hand,
另一方面
the farther our point is from the black line,
点离黑线越远
the more drastic these probabilities are.
它的概率就越大
Points that are well into the blue area get very high probabilities,
完全位于蓝色区域的点概率很高
such as this point with an 85% probability of being blue.
例如这个点有 85% 的概率是蓝色
And points that are well into the red region are given very low probabilities,
完全位于红色区域的点概率很低
such as this point on the bottom that is given a 20% probability of being blue.
例如位于图底部的这个点有 20% 的概率是蓝色
The points over the line are all given a 50% probability of being blue.
位于直线上的点都有 50% 的概率位于蓝色区域
As you can see the probability is a function of the distance from the line.
可以看出 概率是关于点离直线距离的函数
The way we move from discrete predictions to continuous,
从离散到连续预测的方法是
is to simply change your activation function from the step function in the left,
将激活函数从左侧的阶跃函数
to the sigmoid function on the right.
变成右侧的 s 函数
The sigmoid function is simply a function which for
对 s 函数输入较大的正数
large positive numbers will give us values very close to one.
将给出非常接近 1 的值
For large negative numbers will give us values very close to zero.
输入较大的负数则给出非常接近 0 的值
And for numbers that are close to zero,
对于接近 0 的数字
it'll give you values that are close to point five.
将给出接近 0.5 的值
The formula is sigmoid effects equals σ(x) = 1/(1 + exp(-x))
s 函数的表达式为 σ(x) = 1/(1 + exp(-x))
So, before our model consisted of a line with a positive region and a negative region.
之前我们的模型是一条直线和正负区域
Now it consists of an entire probability space or for each point in the plane
现在则包含了整个概率空间
we are given the probability that the label of the point is one for the blue points,
或者说 对于平面中每个点
and zero for the red points.
都能用概率表示它的归属 1 代表蓝点 0 代表红点
For example, for this point the probability of
例如 对于这个点
being blue is 50% and of being red is 50%.
属于蓝色和红色区域的概率各是 50%
For this point, the probabilities are 40% for being blue,
对于这个点 属于蓝色的概率是 40%
and 60% for being red.
属于红色的概率是 60%
For this one over here it's 30% for blue,
对于这个点 属于蓝色概率是 30%
and 70% for red.
属于红色概率是 70%
And for this point all over here is 80% for being
对于这个点 属于蓝色概率是 80%
blue and 25 percent for being red.
属于红色概率是 20%
The way we obtain this probability space is very simple.
获得这种概率空间的方法很简单
We just combine the linear function WX + b with the sigmoid function.
我们只是将线性方程 WX + b 的结果输入 s 函数
So in the left we have the lines that represent the points for which WX + b is
左侧是表示 WX + b 分别等于
zero, one, two, minus one, minus two, etc.
0 1 2 -1 -2 等等的直线
And once we apply the sigmoid function to each of these values in the plane,
对平面中的每个值应用 s 型函数后
we then obtain numbers from zero to one for each point.
获得每个点的数字（0 到 1 之间）
These numbers are just the probabilities of the point being blue.
这些数字表示该点属于蓝色的概率
The probability of the point being blue is a prediction of
这个概率是
the model Y hat to sigmoid of W x plus b.
预测模型：ŷ = σ(Wx + b) 的结果
Here we can see the lines for which the prediction is point five,
可以看出 每个线性估计部分的值分别是 0.5
point six, point seven,
0.6 和 0.7
point four, point three, et cetera.
0.4 0.3 等等
As you can see, as we get more into the blue area,
当我们越往蓝色区域前进
σ(Wx + b) gets closer and closer to one.
σ(Wx + b) 就越来越接近 1
And as we move into the red area,
越往红色区域前进
σ(Wx + b) gets closer and closer to zero.
σ(Wx + b) 就越接近 0
When we're over the main line,
点位于中央直线时
W x plus b is zero,
Wx + b 为 0
which means sigmoid of W s plus b is exactly zero point five.
意味着 σ(Wx + b) 刚好是 0.5
So here on the left we have our old perceptron with
左图是原来的感知器
the activation function as a step function.
激活函数是阶跃函数
And on the right we have our new perceptron,
右侧是新的感知器
where the activation function is the sigmoid function.
激活函数是 s 函数
What our new perceptron does,
新的感知器
it takes the inputs,
接收输入数据后
multiplies them by the weights in the edges and adds the results,
将数据乘以箭头边上所示的权重 并将结果相加
then applies the sigmoid function.
然后应用 s 型函数
So instead of returning one and zero like before it returns
得到的结果不再是之前那样的 1 或 0
values between zero and one such as 0.99 or 0.67 etc.
而是返回一个介于 0 到 1 之间的值 例如 0.99 0.67 等等
Before it used to say the student got accepted or not,
之前可以说学生是否被录取
and now it says the probability of the student got accepted is this much.
现在是说的是学生被录取的概率有多大